Contact

DHA Lahore +923037398641 (Mobile) shahid.rahman47@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shahid-rahman-940bab60 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Web Development PHP JavaScript

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Urdu (Full Professional)

Certifications

Web Application Development in PHP

SHAHID U RAHMAN

Software Engineer at Computan
Lahore

Summary

Experienced FULL STACK PHP LARAVEL /YII2 DEVELOPER with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in PHP(Yii2 & LARAVEL), MYSQL, JAVASCRIPT, BOOTSTRAP4, JQUERY, HTML5, CSS3, XHTML, Web Design, Web Engineering, and HTML. Strong engineering professional with a Certification of PHP Web Application Development focused in Web Development from EVS Provisional Training Institute.

Experience

Computan Senior Software Engineer May 2021 - Present (11 months) Lahore District, Punjab, Pakistan

Triixa
FULL STACK PHP LARAVEL DEVELOPER
January 2021 - May 2021 (5 months)
Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan

Renegade Furniture Group junior Backend Developer Laravel March 2020 - January 2021 (11 months) Islamabad

Xerobug Technologies Software Engineer Yii / Yii2 July 2016 - February 2020 (3 years 8 months) VEHARI

Software Engineer Web

Brain Group of Collages
PHP Web Application Teacher
February 2016 - June 2016 (5 months)

Lahore

Teaching PHP, MySQL, HTML5, CSS3, JQuery

Hi Tech Security Products
Accountant
February 2015 - January 2016 (1 year)
Islamabad

Cash & Bank Books Accounts

Daily Patty Cash book

Costumers & Employees Ledgers Accounts

Rahmat Ullah Malik & Co Computer Operater April 2013 - May 2014 (1 year 2 months) Lahore

Administration Responsibilities

Daily Expenses recodes

Data Entry of Income Tex & Sale Tex Books

Education

Minhaj University Lahore $\mbox{Master of Information Technology} \; , \; \mbox{Computer Systems Networking and} \; \mbox{Telecommunications} \; \cdot \; (2012 - 2013)$

E V S Lahore

Certification of PHP Web Application Development, Web Application Development PHP \cdot (2015 - 2016)

University of the Punjab

Bachelor of Commerce - BCom, Business Administration and Management, General · (March 2007 - April 2010)